Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
I'm not sleepy and there is
no place I'm going to
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
In the jingle jangle morning
I'll come following you
Though I know that evening's
empire has returned into sand
Vanished from my hand
Left me blindly here to stand
but still not sleeping
My weariness amazes me,
I'm branded on my feet
I have no one to meet
And the ancient empty street's
too dead for dreaming
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
I'm not sleepy and there is
no place I'm going to
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
In the jingle jangle morning
I'll come following you
Take me on a trip upon your
magic swirling ship
My senses have been stripped
My hands can't feel to grip
My toes too numb to step
Wait only for my boot heels
to be wandering
I'm ready to go anywhere,
I'm ready for to fade
Into my own parade
Cast your dancing spell my way,
I promise to go under it
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
I'm not sleepy and there is
no place I'm going to
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
In the jingle jangle morning
I'll come following you
Though you might hear
laughing, spinning,
swinging madly across the sun
It's not aimed at anyone
It's just escaping on the run
And but for the sky there are
no fences facing
And if you hear vague traces
of skipping reels of rhyme
To your tambourine in time
It's just a ragged clown behind
I wouldn't pay it any mind
It's just a shadow you're
seeing that he's chasing
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
I'm not sleepy and there is
no place I'm going to
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
In the jingle jangle morning
I'll come following you
And take me disappearing
through the smoke rings
of my mind
Down the foggy ruins of time
Far past the frozen leaves
The haunted frightened trees
Out to the windy beach
Far from the twisted
reach of crazy sorrow
Yes, to dance beneath
the diamond sky
With one hand waving free
Silhouetted by the sea
Circled by the circus sands
With all memory and fate
Driven deep beneath the waves
Let me forget about today
until tomorrow
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
I'm not sleepy and there is no
place I'm going to
Hey! Mr. Tambourine man,
play a song for me
In the jingle jangle morning
I'll come following you